Pietro Belluschi Papers
Pietro Belluschi Papers
- Correspondence-subject files, 1991 accession
  - Juries etc.
    - Boston juries, parcel 8, 3 folders (Box 531)
Bank of Commerce, Oregon, NY, OR 411
Bank of Selwood 456
Bank of Teton Valley, Rexburg, ID 1060
Bank of Toppenish [no number]
Bank of Vernonia, Vernonia, OR 421
Bank of Woodburne, Woodburne, OR 338
Bankers Trust Building, New York, NY [no number]
Banks, L. R. summer house, Oak Grove, OR [no number]
Barracks, demountable 717
Bates Garage (alternate title: Bates Motoramp), Portland, OR 903
Bates Playroom, Portland, OR 1010
Bay Ocean Hotel [no number]
Beach, J. G. 140
Beall Pipe and Tank Corp., Portland, OR 872
Beals Building, Tillamook, OR [no number]
Beauty Shop for PPG [Pittsburgh Plate Glass] 825
Beaverton War Memorial, Beaverton, OR 1005
Beck, F. house [no number]
Bedell Building [no number]
Beebe, W. B. house312 342 373
Bell, J. F. house 1
Belluschi farmhouse alterations, Portland, OR 1134
Belluschi house, Dunthoyne 1078
Belvail, Frank house, Pendleton, OR [no number]
Bennington College Library, Bennington, VT [no number]
Benson Hotel, [unspecified]413 537 612 [no number]
Benson Hotel, alterations to Basements and Toilet Rooms 1117
Benson Hotel, alterations, Portland, OR 494
Benson Hotel, house alterations 902
Benson Hotel, air conditioning plant, Portland, OR 598
Benson Hotel, elevators 1225
Benson Hotel, locker and toilet, Portland, OR 693
Benson Hotel, marquee, Portland, OR 593
Benson Hotel, sidewalk alterations, Portland, OR 1083
Berni Brothers Merchandise Mart, Portland, OR 897
Berni house, Portland, OR 906
Biddle, Spencer house Portland, OR 365
Bingham, G. G. house [no number]
Bitar Bros. Factory & Warehouse / Doughnut Corporation of America, Portland, OR 963
Black, Johnson, and Kendall Office Alteration 1041
Blacksmith Cresent Public School, North York, Ontario [no number]
Blaine Investment Co. alterations, Portland, OR 948
Blair Building alterations, Camas, WA 424
Blitz Weinhard Company alterations 1073
Block development, Yamhill, OR [Urban planning] [no number]
Blodgett, [John] Jr. house Santa Barbara, CA 1111
Blodgett, Portland, OR [Commercial] [no number]
Blossom Music Center Pavilion, Cleveland, OH [no number]
Blyth and Co. (Pacific Building), Portland, OR 499
Board of Trade Building [no number]
Boiler-Makers Union Building, Portland, OR 705
Boise Department Store 465
Boley, Paul house alterations, Oswego, OR 1222
Bond, Goodwin and Tucker alterations, U. S. Bank Building 470
Booth Property parking lot [no number]
Borg-Warner-Johnson prefabricated housing project [Exhibition] 1070
Boston City Hall, Boston, MA [no number]
Boston Company Building, Boston, MA [no number]
Boston, downtown, Boston, MA [Urban planning] [no number]
Boston, north, Boston, MA [Urban planning] [no number]
Bowles, J. R. house 398
Boy Scout Headquarters [no number]
Braley and Graham alterations 945
Brewster, W. L. house21 39 [no number]
Brewster, W. L. house alterations 102
Brewster, William Jr. house 1074
Broadway and Oak St. [unnamed building], Portland, OR993 [no number]
Broadway Bank 395
Broadway Bank Building 396
Broadway Boot Shop alterations, Portland, OR 925
Broadway Dyers and Cleaners Building [no number]
Broadway Theatre, Portland, OR 437
Broadway-Hazelwood, Portland, OR [Commercial] 434
Brockton Housing, Pine Grove, Brockton, MA [no number]
Brodsen's Furniture, Forest Grove, OR 930
Bronaugh, E. C. [no number]
Brooder House office for Brownell 627
Brooklyn Museum, Italian exhibit, Brooklyn, NY [no number]
Brooksales, Inc. offices [no number]
Brown, Sam H., apartments [no number]
Brownell, Barry house 763
Brownsville Woollen Mills Store alterations [no number]
Bruhn, Frank house [no number]
Buck Ambulance, Portland, OR 900
Buck Ranch House 892
Building, 11th and Adler 941
Building, Lownsdale & Washington [Commercial] [no number]
Bungalow in front of water tower [no number]
Burg, Charles F. house alterations [no number]
Burgman and Adams Lab., Portland, OR 553
Burke, Louis [Residential?] 50
Burke, Louis house [no number]
Burkes, D. C. house 822
Burlington Mall Road [no number]
Butler Bank, Hood River, OR 388
Butler Building, Hood River [no number]
Buyer's Building alterations [no number]
C. B. Fernald Building [no number]
Cabell, Henry house [no number]
Cambridge Building [no number]
Camp Adainton, recreation center for enlisted personnel [no number]
Camp Fire Girls summer camp, Clackama River, OR [no number]
Campbell, Clark & Wolf Clinic Building, Salem, OR 999
Campbell, Dr., clinic, Salem, OR 1179
Campbell, Dr., house alterations 1181
Canadian Bank of Commerce [no number]
Canadian Corp for 1967 World Expo [no number]
Canadian Legion Convention [no number]
Canadian Pacific Railroad offices, American Bank Building, Portland, OR506 575
Cascade Building, Selling [no number]
Caswell, W. R. house 848
Catlin School, Portland, OR1172 894
Catlin, Seth house [no number]
C-C Stores (D. Bates), Vancouver WA 672
Cedar Hills solar house 1168
Cedar Lane Unitarian Church, Bethesda, MD [no number]
Cedar Realty house [no number]
Central Building alterations 556
Central Building entrance, Portland, OR 488
Central Library alterations 1043
Central Lutheran Church, [unspecified], Eugene, OR 934
Central Lutheran Church, parish house, Eugene, OR 1112
Central Lutheran Church, parsonage, Eugene, OR 1068
Central Lutheran Church, [unspecified], Portland, OR 924
Central National Bank 502
Central National Bank alterations [no number]
Century City, Los Angeles, CA [no number]
Chamber of Commerce 933
Chamber of Commerce additions to mezzanine 884
Chamber of Commerce alterations, Portland, OR 679
Chapman house [no number]
Charles Berg Store alterations [no number]
Charleston Center, Charleston, SC [no number]
Charleston Shopping Center, Portland, OR 1188
Charlesworth Building, Portland, OR [no number]
Chase, Mr. and Mrs. H. A. house 578
Cheney house 577
Christ the King Church, Milwaukie, OR 313
Christenson Oil Plant, OR [no number]
Church at Mildura, Victoria, Australia [no number]
Church of the Christian Union, Rockford, IL [no number]
Church of the People (aka People's Church), Seattle, WA 936
Church of the Redeemer, Baltimore, MD [no number]
Cigar stand, Equitable Building 1092
Citizen's Branch, Safety Deposit Lobby alterations, Portland, OR 1232
City Hall alterations 600
Civic Center, Portland, OR [no number]
Clark Art Institute, Williamstown, MA 6608
Clark Bros. Store, American Bank Building, Portland, OR 501
Clark County National Bank [no number]
Clark house alterations [no number]
Clarke Florist 530
Clearwater Plumbing 1130
Clinic, Albany, OR 1008
Cloud Cap Inn, Mt. Hood, OR 449
Coats Netants Bay house 703
Cobbs, F. J. house 234
Cochran, K. R. house 665
Coe, R. C. house, Woodburn, OR [no number]
Collins house, Chester, CA 1052
Collins Pine Co. Recreation Building 1118
Collins Sales Building 688
Collins, C. W. 3
Collins, Truman, clinic, Chester, OR 1051
Colombia Theatre alterations [no number]
Colonial Estates, Springfield, MA 6716
Colonial Stores [no number]
Columbia Brick Works, Portland, OR 869
Columbia Building lobby alterations 490
Columbia Point, Boston, MA [Urban planning] [no number]
Comfort Stations, Defense Housing Project, Vancouver, WA [no number]
Commercial development (proposed), Salem, OR [no number]
Commonwealth Building, Portland, OR1020 520 547
Commonwealth Inc. 539
Commonwealth Inc. Night Club [no number]
Commonwealth Space, Equitable Building 1091
Commonwealth Trust & Title [no number]
Community Church at Adams OR, Adams, OR [no number]
Concordia College, Portland, OR [no number]
Continental Oil Co. Service Station [no number]
Cooch Building, Parker Schramm [no number]
Coos Bay Lumber Co. alterations 992
Corbett Building alterations, Portland, OR 651
Corbett Building, Portland, OR [no number]
Corbett Estate188 [no number]
Corbett Estate hotel garage alterations, Portland, OR 1095
Corbett Estate motor ramp garage, Portland, OR 447
Corbett, [E. R. or H. L.?] 65
Corbett, E. R. [Residential?] 125
Corbett, E. R. house alterations [no number]
Corbett, H. L. house alterations357 [no number]
Corbett, H. L., Mrs. house 467
Corbett, Hamilton, Palatine Hill house 482
Corbett-O'Shea (Lipmann-Wolf)83 95
Cornelius Hotel alterations (proposed) house [no number]
Corvallis High School, Corvallis, OR [no number]
Corvallis Public Library (proposed), Corvallis, OR 533
Corvallis Telephone & Telegraph Company, Corvallis, OR 1175
Courtemanche house alterations, McMinnville, OR 1154
Courtemanche, L. A., farm implements service building, McMinnville, OR 841
Courtemanche, L. A., warehouse and display building, McMinnville, OR 1180
Courtney fireplace [no number]
Crocker, Anna B. seaside cottage 241
Crocker, Anna B., house, Portland, OR 471
Cromwell Tailors, Portland, OR1109 932
Crooker [possibly Crocker?] house [no number]
Crown-Willamette Paper Co. office 263
Crown-Willamette Paper Co. mills 268
Crown-Willamette Paper Co. Portland, OR 397
Crown-Zellerbach alterations for Pittock Block (proposed), Portland, OR [no number]
Curators Residence, Champoeg State Park, Champoeg, OR 1227
Curry, C. E. house361 44
Daily Courier Newspaper Plant, Grants Pass, OR 1057
Daily News Building dining room (proposed) [no number]
Dant & Russell, Equitable Building, Portland, OR 1116
Dantone Industrial Plant, Dant & Russell, Portland, OR 1107
Daughters of Washington Log Building [no number]
Davidson Bakery alterations, Portland, OR 681
Davidson house [no number]
De Graaf house addition (proposed), Sandy, OR (Portland) [no number]
De Hart, E. J. house [no number]
Dean Witter & Co. 661
Dean Witter, Equitable Building 1169
DeCico Building 846
Del Monte Corporation headquarters building, San Francisco, CA [no number]
Densmoor [or Densmore] house, Albany, OR 947
Detention Home for Women, Troutdale, OR 224
Developments of two city blocks, Portland OR [Urban planning] 1200
Devereaux, E. L. house [no number]
Dewey Square Office Building, Boston, MA [no number]
Dickson house 363
Dinwiddie Couples Housing DFH, Portland, OR 715
Disciples of Christ, Cedar Hills, OR [no number]
Doll House, Junior League, Portland, OR [no number]
Dorchester, Boston, MA [Urban planning] [no number]
Dorena Dam project 997
Dormitory apartments for war workers [no number]
Doyle Cottage, Neah-Kah-Nie, OR [no number]
Doyle family headstones [no number]
Doyle property, Morrison St. [no number]
Doyle, A. E. house [no number]
Doyle, Portland, OR [no number]
Drake Apartment House, Portland, OR [no number]
Drake development, Portland, OR 878
Drake, Wyman and Voss alterations, U. S. Bank Building 477
Dresser Industries [no number]
Drummond-Storey Dog and Cat Hospital, Portland, OR 1138
E. May, Baker Theatre Arcade 189
Early, Charles house [no number]
East Side Plating Works, Portland, OR 926
Eastside Branch Library, Portland, OR124 29
Edergerton, Germeshausen, and Grier Inc. [EG&G defense contractor], Bedford, MA [no number]
Edison Building909 970
Edwards, J. G. house 433
Ehrman, E. cottage, Columbia River Highway 252
Electrical Distributing Co., Portland, OR1163 929
Ellis-Schiller Co. Garage, Pendleton, OR [no number]
Embarcadero Center, San Francisco Development Agency, San Francisco, CA [no number]
Emmanuel Lutheran Church, Longview, WA 994
Equitable Building, penthouse 1183
Equitable Savings and Loan Association, Portland, OR540 6301 890 [no number]
Esther Foster Shops, for Paul Wallace, Salem, OR 870
Ethyl Walker School, Simsbury, CT [no number]
Eugene Hotel addition, Eugene, OR 1099
Eugene Prop., Eugene, OR 643
Eugene store building 662
Eutaw Place Baptist Church, Baltimore, MD [no number]
Evans, Dr. John house [no number]
Everatte house 802
Everson Museum of Art, Syracuse, NY [no number]
Eyre, David house 1136
F. S. D. Elevator Doors 475
Failing, H. E. [no number]
Fairbanks-Morse house alterations 1025
Farmhouse alterations 842
Federal Office Building, Architectural Competition [no number]
Federal Reserve Bank [no location given] [no number]
Federal Reserve Bank of Philadelphia, Philadelphia, PA [no number]
Federal Reserve Bank of San Francisco, Portland Branch, Portland, OR 1000
Federal Reserve Bank, Boston, Boston, MA [no number]
Ferris Apartments, Ketchikan, AK [no number]
Fertex Display Booth, Housing Show 567
Feves, Dr., clinic, Pendleton, OR 1040
Fields, L. R. ranch house 441
Fifth Ave. shop 549
Firestone Equipment Co. (L. A. Courtemanche), Los Angeles, CA 1067
Firestone Sales and Service Shop [no number]
First Community Church (proposed), Columbus, OH [no number]
First Lutheran Church of Boston [no number]
First Methodist Church, Duluth, MN 1726
First Methodist Church, Portland, OR 794
First National Bank, [no location given] [no number]
First National Bank of Boise, Boise, ID 466
First National Bank of Portland, Salem branch, Salem, OR [no number]
First National Bank, 6th and Taylor 385
First National Bank, Camas, Camas, WA [no number]
First National Bank, Coquille 75
First National Bank, Hermiston, Hermiston, OR 974
First National Bank, Klamath, Klamath Falls, OR [no number]
First National Bank, Vancouver, WA 548
First Presbyterian Church [no location given] [no number]
First Presbyterian Church, Cottage Grove, OR 1124
First Presbyterian Church, Portland, OR 66
Fisher & Thorson Store alterations [no number]
Flat Building, Belmont and 68th, for Philip Hart, Portland, OR [no number]
Florence Distribution Co. Office / Menduni Warehouse and Sales Building 1149
Flynn, J. L. house, Oswego, OR 796
Folding Chair / Table Combination [Furniture] [no number]
Ford Building [no number]
Ford Chairs [Furniture] [no number]
Ford Foundation [no number]
Ford Motor Co. service plant, Portland OR 159
Ford Motor Co., Dearborn, MI [no number]
Forest rangers cabin, Eagle Creek [no number]
Fort Meyer Post Chapel, Ft. Myers, VA [no number]
Fort Point Channel Study, Boston, MA [Urban planning] [no number]
Fort Richardson, Field House, Alaska 1220
Frank, S. 93
Franks, garage and monument [no number]
Franz house 630
Freiberg, William house [no number]
Frye house 939
Ft. Richardson enlisted men's barracks, Ft. Richardson, AK1186 1187 1191 1204
Ft. Richardson enlisted men's service club, Ft. Richardson, AK 1185
Fuller, W. P., warehouse, Portland, OR 266
G.E. Building alterations, Portland, OR 684
Gabriel Fabrication and Erection Co., Portland, OR 877
Gallucci [Belluschi?] house, Portland, OR 840
Garage 293
Garage, Astoria, OR [no number]
Gardner, John house [no number]
General Telephone Company, Tampa, FL [no number]
Glencoe School, Multnomah Cty, OR 410
Golasuonno, Thomas house addition [no number]
Gold Beach Resort, Gold Beach, OR [no number]
Goldendale Library, Goldendale, WA 208
Goodaire [no number]
Gordon, E. G. house [no number]
Goucher College, Towson, MD[no number] 4103 4144
Graham-Kearney-Pierce, Seattle, WA 479
Grandale Realty Company Building [no number]
Great Northern Railroad 1066
Greeley, Charles H. Garage [no number]
Grelle, C. E. [no number]
Griffith Apartments 448
Griffith, A. G. house Oswego, OR 1203
Gripper, J. C. house [no number]
Grossman [or Grossmayer] Co. 541
Guaranty Building (aka Burr Conrad Broom Co.) 443
Gumbert Furs alterations, Portland, OR 995
Hacket, W. H., apartment house [no number]
Haines Foster Bakery [no number]
Hammond, Ross C. Office, Portland, OR [Commercial] 727
Hanley, [William?] 61
Harmon 38
Harris Ice Machine Works [no number]
Harry Hawkins Store, Hawkins-Roberts Building, Salem, OR 1110
Hartman and Thompson 33
Hartman, J. L. house [no number]
Hawaiian Electric Company, Honolulu, HI [no number]
Hawk, H., autopark at High and Ferry, Salem, OR 1194
Hawkins, Harry house 1004
Hazelwood Building, Portland, OR392 468
Heathman Hotel Garage, Portland, OR 590
Herbert, Bow highway hotel 956
Higgins, E. A. house, Astoria, OR 285
Hill, Dr., apartments and office, Salem, OR 899
Hilmar Pabst house [no number]
Hinman, John house, Pelham Manor, NY [no number]
Hirsch Building 977
Hirsch Residence alterations (proposed) [no number]
Hoehne, Mark E. house Longview, WA1224 [no number]
Hoffman Apartments [no number]
Hoffman Garage 455
Hoffman Hotel Building, Store alterations, Eugene, OR [no number]
Holladay School, Portland, OR 378
Holman-Lutz Mortuary, garage, Portland, OR 523
Holman-Lutz Mortuary, Portland, OR492 557 [no number]
Holtz, Aaron house 432
Holy Family Parish, Portland, OR 866
Holy Redeemer Parish convent, Portland, OR 1137
Holy Redeemer Parish school building, Oakland, CA 1128
Honeyman Hardware362 41
Honeyman Hardware alterations [no number]
Hood River Courthouse, Hood River, OR 904
Horizontal Construction 724
Hosford Elementary School [no number]
Hospital, Hood River, OR [no number]
Hotel (proposed) for Hoffman [no number]
Hotel (proposed) for Reese [no number]
Hotel (proposed), Portland, OR [no number]
House at Linwood Heights, Chamber of Commerce, Vancouver, WA 1160
House for Parents Magazine, Portland, OR 960
Housing development (proposed), Eugene, OR [no number]
Housing project at Cedar Hills, Cedar Hills, OR 1167
Housing project at Indian Hill, Tacoma, WA 985
Housing project for Vista Corp. [no number]
Housing project, Vista Ave., Portland, OR 637
Howard house [no number]
Hulbert house 635
Humke [no number]
Huntington-Malarky [or Hunt Malarkey] house, Sun Valley, ID 1131
Hurley's Store, American Bank Building, Salem, OR 622
Hurley's Store, Equitable Building 1093
Idaho Statesman, Boise, NY, ID 1081
Immanuel Lutheran Church, Silverton, OR 989
Imperial Hotel, Portland, OR [no number]
Industrial development site, Concord Road, Billerica, MA [no number]
Inner Harbor development, Baltimore, MD [Urban planning] [no number]
International Wool Secretariat [no number]
Iron Firemen Display Building, Portland, OR 966
Irvington Garage & Auto [no number]
Isom Cottage, Neah-Kah-Nie, OR [no number]
Italian Importing Co. Warehouse, Angelo Bocci, Portland, OR 1062
J. C. Penney Building [no number]
J. L. Bowman Hotel at Camp Arrah Wanna, Welches, OR [no number]
J. L. Hudson and Associates Housing project, Richland, WA 1104
J. P. Finley Mortuary alterations, Portland, OR 573
J. P. Finley Mortuary parking lot, Portland, OR 1012
J. P. Finley Mortuary, Portland, OR 513
Jack Cody's restaurant, Equitable Building 1046
Jack, Dr. house alterations, East Moreland [no number]
Jeffrey, O. K. [no number]
Jehlinger Store alterations [no number]
Jessup, Bertram E. house 944
Johnson shop, Salem, OR 1212
Johnson, E. H. house, Orenko, OR 1197
Johnson, G. H. house alterations [no number]
Joss, Philip house1108 667
Judd, F. E. house [no number]
Juilliard School of Music, New York, NY [no number]
Kage, F. H. 25
Kah-nee-tah Resort, Warm Springs, OR [no number]
Kelly's Restaurant, Morgan Building [no number]
Kendall Community Church [no number]
Kennicott, G. W. house alterations [no number]
Kerr, Peter, beach cottage, Gearhart, OR 701
Kerr, Peter, house, Elk Rock, OR 962
Keystone Building, Boston, MA [no number]
Kiernan Garage, Portland, OR [no number]
Kiggins, John [no number]
King Estate [no number]
King Hill Apartments 568
Knights of Columbus [no number]
Kootenay Industrial School [no number]
Kortin Music Co., Longview, WA 839
Kroeker, J. D. house, Oak Grove, OR 1202
Kuhns, R. A. house [no number]
La France Wine Company, Venuti Warehouse, Portland, OR 1007
Labbe Estate Warehouse [no number]
Labby [or Labbe], Daniel house 1026
Ladd and Bush Bank, Salem, OR 668
Ladd Estate, Portland, OR [no number]
Lafayette Building for Foreman and Clark, Portland, OR 640
LaGuardia High School [no number]
Lalew Telephone Building [no number]
Lane Investment Company alterations 1195
Law Building (proposed), Portland, OR [no number]
Lawrence Warehouse Office Alteration 1042
Lee house, Brookline, MA [no number]
Lennon's Store, Sherman Clay Building, Morrison St. 340
Lenox Square Shopping Center [no number]
Leo Ryan Lumber Co. Offices, Portland, OR [no number]
Lerner Shops, Property alterations, Portland, OR 905
Leta Haley and John Vitas, American Bank Building, Portland, OR 546
Lewis & Clark Exposition candy booth [no number]
Lewis Building alterations 1031
Lewis, A. G. house [no number]
Lewis, Percy W. house 580
Lewthwaite, A. J. house [no number]
Liberty St. Building, Salem, OR 1144
Library Associaton Art Room alterations, Portland, OR 1146
Library Associaton of Portland, Portland, OR 1115
LIFE Magazine House [Exhibition] 973
Lincoln Center, New York, NY [no number]
Lincoln County Bank, Toledo, OR 350
Lincoln High School Memorial Tablets 418
Linfield College, [unspecified], McMinnville, OR1044 836 [no number]
Linfield College, Administration Building 404
Linfield College, athletic Center, McMinnville, OR 1189
Linfield College, bridges, McMinnville, OR 525
Linfield College, expansion program 1161
Linfield College, Fine Arts Building 920
Linfield College, gym, McMinnville, OR 291
Linfield College, infirmary, McMinnville, OR 854
Linfield College, Library, McMinnville, OR 570
Linfield College, Pioneer Hall, McMinnville, OR 954
Lipman, Wolfe & Co.438 1050 [no number]
Lister cottage house alterations [no number]
Littman, Fred house 1061
Lloyd Building [no number]
Lockwood, A. F. house [no number]
Lockwood, S. P. garage [no number]
Longview Bank, Longview, WA [no number]
Longview Daily News, Longview, WA 1064
Lowengart & Co. [no number]
Lowenson alterations (Stevens Building) [Commercial] 923
Loyal B. Stearns Memorial Fountain, Portland, OR 686
Lumbermen's Building Alteration 1129
Lundstrum, K. G. 22
Lutheran Chapel and student center, Philadelphia, PA [no number]
Lynch, M. J. house [no number]
Lynridge House at Cedar Hills, Cedar Hills, OR 1170
MacGraw, Don house, Portland, OR 426
MacGuire reception room 634
Madden, George house [no number]
Maegley-Tichner alterations, Portland, OR 639
Magnin Store, Portland, OR [no number]
Magsaysay Building, Manila, Philippines [no number]
Maine Savings Bank, Portland, ME [no number]
Majestic Hotel alterations, Automobile Service Co., Portland, OR 692
Malarkey house [no number]
Malarkey, Don/Dan house 53
Malarky House house 971
Mann & Mann Store, Central Building 521
Mannings Coffee Shop, Proposed alterations [no number]
Marble Institute of America, Santa Fe, NM [no number]
Maren Gribscov building (restaurant), Bend, OR 1045
Marion County Courthouse, Salem, OR 1125
Marion Hotel alterations, Salem, OR 1121
Marion Hotel Tavern 1133
Marlborough DCA Subsidized Housing Competition, Marlborough, MA [no number]
Marsh House, Columbia, NY, OR 689
Marshall, G. L. house 509
Marshfield American Bank, Marshfield, OR 405
Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT), Cambridge, MA [no number]
Massachusetts Turnpike Authority, Weston, MA [no number]
Mathis Apartment House Project 1140
May Apartments [no number]
May Memorial Unitarian Church, Syracuse, NY 6125
Mayfair Theatre Entrance, Portland, OR 1035
McCullouch, Charles house 579
McGowan, A. H. house [no number]
McGowan, H. S., store, Astoria, OR [no number]
McKinley National Memorial [no number]
McLean Apartments 832
McLoughlin Heights Shopping Center [no number]
McMorran and Washburne store, Eugene, OR461 [no number]
McNaughton Property Development, Portland, OR 658
Mead, Stephen, Estate of 143
Meade Building alterations, Portland, OR 1230
Mears, [S. M.?] house 77
Medford Shopping Center (proposed), Skidmore Owings & Merrill [no number]
Medical Arts Center Building, Eugene, OR 517
Meier and Frank multipurpose building1199 40 [no number]
Meier, Abe house alterations 244
Meier, J. L. house [no number]
Meier, Jack house alterations 979
Meir [or Meien], Allen house 400
Menefee [or Menifee] house, Yamhill, OR 891
Merry house [no number]
Methodist Church 911
Metropolitan Museum Exhibit, New York, NY [no number]
Mexico Hotel, Mazatlan, Mexico [no number]
Meyers, H. M. house, Seattle, WA 673
Miami Center condo and garage, Miami, FL [no number]
Miles, Robinson [or Robinson, Miles] house, Walla Walla, WA 1155
Miller Drug Store, Equitable Building 1084
Miller, H. A. house, Dufur, OR 669
Mills, Lewis house [no number]
Minneapolis Apartment Tower, Knudson, Minneapolis, MN [no number]